[Music]
Hey, y'all, I'm Campbell.
I'm Ivy.
I'm Madison.
And we're all sophomores.
It's actually funny.
We all met in the spring before coming
to Ole Miss at a grad party in Dallas.
After the grad party,
we all stayed in touch,
and I just knew they were gonna
be our best friends in college.
Going into rush week, we were
pretty conflicted and just getting
pulled in so many different
directions from other people.
Every time I left Chi O
and every time I walked past
it on the way to Martin,
I just wanted to go back.
I loved it so much.
I would, like, see the rush chairs
at the top of the steps just,
like, smiling, and I was like,
I want to be there.
I remember going into Madison's room
during rush week and just asking
her if she felt the same level
of comfort and peace at Chi O as I did,
and when she did, I was so happy,
and I knew that's where we wanted to be.
I remember feeling all
the pressure from everyone,
and I just, like, walked into
Chi O and just felt home.
It's truly a testament of what Chi O is.
You'll never stop making friends.
[Music]
Hi, I'm Kennedy Bryant.
I'm from Frisco, Texas.
And I'm Alexa Beatty,
and I'm from Lawrence, Kansas.
Being out of state,
both of us didn't really know a lot
of people coming to Ole Miss
from our high schools.
I moved around my whole life, so I didn't
know anyone except for the Rebelettes.
We were actually set up by some of our
mutual friends to be roommates in Crosby,
and I just remember when we first met,
we instantly became best friends.
It was just such a blessing to come into
somewhere new, and it being so scary
with college and everything,
just to feel like
you already have your person was so lucky.
Going into rush week,
me and Kennedy actually
decided not to tell each other anything
we were doing,
just because we wanted to choose
for ourselves where we found our home.
And for me, every time I walked into Chi O,
I felt that genuineness across the room.
And I just knew that that's
where I needed to be.
The opening of our bids and finding
each other in the Grove and getting
to run home with each other was
just one of my favorite memories.
It felt really special,
both choosing for ourselves but
knowing this is both where
we're meant to be together.
[Music]
On bid day, we actually went
to the Chi O retreat together.
We didn't know a soul on that bus.
We had no clue what was going on,
and now those are some of our best friends.
I don't think I could have gone through
college without Kennedy by my side.
I really, it's really
just the little moments
that really make
our friendship so special.
[Music]
So now we've gone from Crosby to the Arbors,
and now we're in the Brown House,
which is a passed-down
house in Chi O, and there's
been years and years
of Chi Os who have lived here.
I really can't thank Chi O
enough for all the friendships
and all the memories that
will truly last a lifetime.
[Music]